是现今世上速度最快的人
and I am the fastest man alive.
在外人看来
To the outside world,
我只是个普通的鉴证专员
I'm an ordinary forensic scientist.
但在尖端科研实验室的朋友们的帮助下
But secretly, with the help of my friends at S.T.A.R. Labs,
我秘密地打击犯罪  寻找跟我一样的超能力者
I fight crime and find other meta-humans like me.
但是我在时间中迷失了
But I became lost in time.
我的朋友们用尽了一切办法才把我救回来
It took everything in my friends' power to bring me back,
但我们的世界也因此出现了新的威胁
and in doing so our world was opened up to new threats.
我是唯一来得及阻止他们的人
And I'm the only one fast enough to stop them.
我是闪电侠
I am the Flash.
《闪电侠》前情回顾
Previously, on "The Flash"...
-我这是怎么了  -拉尔夫·德比
- What happened to me? - Ralph Dibny...
-他曾经是个警察  -脏警
- He used to be a cop. - Dirty cop.
我是一名优秀的侦探
I was a good detective!
-这不是我的世界  -所以地球二是咯
- This is not my world. - Oh, and Earth-2 is?
你在那里交了很多我不知道的朋友吗
Did you make a bunch of friends there that I don't know about?
你说你曾是个好警察
You said you were a good cop.
现在就当好警察吧
Be one.
-让我训练你  -做什么
- Let me train you. - For what?
做我做的事
To do what I do.
你当初为什么调查贝洛斯市长
What made you look into Mayor Bellows?
是个客户  他的姓是迪沃
Oh, it was a client. Last name DeVoe.
欠你一杯咖啡  菜鸟
Owe you for the java, rookie.
简直不敢相信我把钱包落在家里了
Can't believe I left my wallet at home.
别客气  能连着落下五次
Don't worry about it. It could happen to anyone...
也是很正常的
five times in a row.
还有你能不能别再叫我菜鸟了
And could you please stop calling me rookie?
抱歉  习惯了
Sorry, old habit
毕竟我以前是你的上司
from when I was your superior officer.
就是在你害我被开除
You know, before you got me fired,
毁了我的事业和生活之前
ruined my career... destroyed my life.
压碎了我的灵魂  让我
Crushed my spirit, left me alone
-一个朋友都没有  -别忘了
- without a friend in the world. - Don't forget how
是我让你变成了一个可伸可缩的大肉团
I turned you into an amorphous, stretchy blob.
这的确是你对我做的一件好事
Actually, that's the one good thing you've done for me.
当然了  你不是
Course, you didn't do it
特意做的  所以得不到我的感谢
on purpose, so you don't get credit.
你们俩  把钱拿出来  快点
Both of you, hand over your cash, now!
等一下  好吗  就一秒
Pardon us, okay? One second.
这个机会很好  我一直在教你  对吧
Okay, this is perfect. I've been teaching you, right?
抢劫犯最适合刚出道的超级英雄了
Muggers are like Superhero 101.
-像我这样的  -你打算怎么办
- Ooh, Ralphy like-y. - All right, what's your plan?
我今天早晨洗澡的时候
Okay, I was thinking about this
想到的  如果变成一个
in the shower this morning: how sweet would it be
巨大的弹弓怎么样
to turn into a giant slingshot?
虽然有点怪  但是也行
That's a weird plan, but okay.
我有个更好的主意
Oh, I got an even cooler idea.
还在抢劫中呢
Hey! I'm still robbing you guys!
马上就好  先生
We will be right with you, sir!
拜托
Please!
能不能做点  时髦的事
Okay, what if I did, like, a human Slinky thing?
把他包起来  扔几下
Maybe wrap him up, throw in a few on-theme puns?
随便吧  拉尔夫  我们得
Whatever, Ralph. We just gotta
-抓紧点时间了  -放松  菜鸟
- hurry up a little bit. - Relax, rookie.
我见过很多歹徒  他不会开枪的
I've seen a lot of thugs. This guy is no shooter.
我的腿
My leg!
好了
Well.
我们的事情做完了
Our work here is done.
你想就这么走了吗  我们不能走
Hey, hey, what are you doing? We can't just leave.
-你打中了他  -开枪的不是我
- You just shot him. - I didn't shoot him.
-他自己开的枪  -我
- He shot him. - Well, I...
你觉得是我开枪打你的吗
Do you feel like I shot you?
别再打他了
Stop shooting him!
我没有开枪
I am not shooting him!
打中了我屁股
Oh, they shot my ass!
他虽然受了点伤  但是
Okay, so he's a little banged up, but...
我们抓到了坏人  这不是超级英雄该做的吗
we caught the bad guy. Isn't that what superheroes do?
不  超级英雄的首要任务是保护市民
No, a superhero's first job is to protect people.
天呐  那次要任务是什么
Oh, God. What's the second job?
不停地说教吗
Long-winded lectures before noon?
我才没有  拿着
I barely... take this.
总有一天  我要把闪电扔到很高
One day, I'm gonna throw a lightning bolt so far up...
我现在带他去医院
I'm taking him to the hospital!
你欠我五杯咖啡
And you owe me five coffees.
没事了
It's fine.
我知道很疼  起来吧
I know. Come on, get up.
我不会伤害你的  这边走
I'm not gonna hurt you. This way, come on.
他没拿枪
Hey! He left his gun!
他已经改过自新了
He's reformed already.
闪 电 侠
第四季
第六集
我们要谈谈
We need to talk.
结局只有一个
The only way it can end...
我获得胜利
with my victory.
什么
What?
好吧  我们慢慢来
Fine. Let us take the long way
继续
and continue.
今天  这是第一次
Today, for the first time,
事情将会发生调整  让闪电侠队
events will align that give Team Flash
有机会发现你的身份
a chance to discover your identity.
这比你预期的要早
This is earlier than you anticipated.
-没关系  -才怪
- It is of no concern. - Like hell!
你知道这样做的风险
You know what's at risk.
我们正在做的事
What we are doing.
如果你计算错误
If you've miscalculated
-即使是一个小数点  -没有小数点
- by even a decimal-- - There is not a decimal,
也没有分数  没有无穷小变量
a fraction, an infinitesimal variable
能躲过我的思维
beyond my thought...
躲过我的思想
beyond my mind.
即使现在
Even now,
这个论点的7798个变量
of the 7,798 variations of this argument,
我都已经预测到了  而且知道它的结局如何
I have anticipated them all and know how it ends.
那结局是什么
Then how does it end?
结局只有一个
The only way it can end.
我获得胜利
With my victory.
真可怜  熬了一夜吧
Ouch. All-nighter?
自从冰霜杀手决定去找火人后
I haven't been this tired since Killer Frost decided
我还从没这么累过
to go to Burning Man.
是吗  我们搜索那个
Yeah? Well, how is our search
神秘的迪沃怎么样了
for the mysterious DeVoe coming?
艾伦  我们搜索了所有的坏人
Allen, we're searching for an evil mastermind.
而我们唯一的线索就是他的名字
The only clue we have to go on is his name,
可是同名的有几千人  你问
of which there's literally thousands, so how's
结果怎么样  简直
the search going? It's...
太好了
fantastic.
真怀念
I missed that.
如果我们想找到迪沃  就需要更多的智慧
If we're gonna find DeVoe, we need more brain power.
你怎么不早说
Well, why didn't you say so?
我这个大师级的侦探  已经做好了准备
One master detective, ready to detect.
我说的是"更多的智慧"
I said "more brain power."
启动紧急氧气净化
Initiating emergency oxygen purge.
系统运作
倒计时开始
十  九
In ten... nine...
八  七  六
eight... seven... six...
五  四
five... four...
等一会
One more second.
二  一
two... one...
我说过  我们需要更多人的帮忙
Like I said, we need more help.
也许我该打电话给我的朋友
Maybe I should call my friends.
-你的什么  -我的朋友
- Your what? - My friends.
他是说朋友吗
Is he saying "Friends"?
我想他是在讽刺
I think he's being sarcastic.
不不不  这是胡言乱语
No, no, no. This is delirium.
他一晚没睡开始精神失常了
He's cracked from being awake all night.
哈里  你所有的朋友都在这房间里
Hey, Harry, all of your friends are in this room.
我还有其他的朋友
I have other friends.
你叫我交新朋友
You asked me to make new friends.
我交了新朋友  那是个任务
I made new friends. It was a task.
-我完成任务了  -太好了
- I complete tasks. - That's so great.
-我等不及要见他们  -哈里  听我说
- I can't wait to meet them. - Harry, you listened to me.
-我真为你感到骄傲  -没什么好骄傲的
- I'm so proud of you. - Okay, there's no pride--
拇指别伸了  我的朋友都很聪明
Put that down. Look, my friends are smart.
他们会帮我们的  我去打给他们
They'll help us. I'll call them.
好吧  在这期间
All right, well, um, in the meantime,
我们要找出公交车上其余的超能力者
we gotta find the rest of these bus metas.
他们和迪沃的计划有关
Somehow they're connected to DeVoe's plan.
你当时在公交车上
You were on the bus.
你记不记得还有谁在上面吗
Can you remember anybody else who was?
受害者
我当时是半醉半醒的状态
Well, I was in between drunk and hungover at the time.
她真可爱  她怎么了
She is cute. What's her deal?
-她在坐牢  -什么时候能去探监
- She's in jail. - When are visiting hours?
那可不可以用震波看看公交车上其余的人
What about vibing the rest of the bus passengers?
我试过了  但是
I mean, I-I tried, but, you know,
我们释放的暗物质
the... the dark matter we released
造成了时空巨变
was such a massive space-time event
导致我的超能力只会反射
that my energy just reflected back
最终我震波了我自己
and I ended up vibing myself.
我很肯定我再次经历了我的出生
I'm pretty sure I relived my own birth.
或者那是我的死亡吗
Or was that my death?
有其他不必受到精神损伤的方法
You know, there are other non-traumatizing ways
能把拉尔夫的记忆带回来
of bringing Ralph's memory back,
-比如说催眠  -真有催眠这种事吗
- like hypnosis. - Is that really a thing?
不是卡通片里看着怀表指针的那种
I mean, not the whole cartoon, pocket watch version,
但是有的  真正的催眠可以用来恢复记忆的
but yeah, real hypnosis can be used to recover memories.
好吧  你知道怎么催眠吗
All right. Do you know any hypnotists?
我不知道
Not me.
-你说卡通片时我已经懵了  -好吧
- You lost me at "Cartoon." - All right.
所以谁要来催眠拉尔夫呢
So who's gonna hypnotize Ralph?
我是莎伦·芬科尔医生
I'm Dr. Sharon Finkel.
芬科尔医生  谢谢你给我们腾出时间
Dr. Finkel, thank you so much for squeezing us in.
我们的朋友拉尔夫现在有点麻烦
Our friend Ralph here is having trouble
他不记得一件案子的
remembering information...
信息  对吗  拉尔夫
for a detective case. Right, Ralph?
那个
So...
中城大学
莎伦·芬科尔
硕士学位
看来你没上过哈佛大学
I see you didn't go to Harvard.
是的  你呢
No. Did you?
我知道你在那儿学到了什么
I see what you did there.
如果你能把他的性格也弄一弄
If you could fix his personality too,
那就太好了
that'd be great.
放弃吧  菜鸟
Give it up, rookie.
这心理专家的胡言乱语对我没用的
This psycho hooey's never gonna work on me.
这倒是很快
Well, that was quick.
现在来回想一下  拉尔夫
Now, remember with me, Ralph.
那是一个月前的事  你在一辆公交车上
It's a month ago. You're on a bus.
你看到了什么
What do you see?
我看到有人...  在哭
I see someone... crying.
那家伙真的让我很不开心
Dude's really bumming me out.
振作点  兄弟
Hey, cheer up, buddy.
你可以的
You can do it.
-你还看到什么  - 我看到几个女人
- What else do you see? - I see... some women.
看不到她们的脸
I can't see their faces.
34-32-36  38-34-32
34-32-36, 38-34-32.
那是公交车路线吗
Are those bus routes?
我认为是那些是三围
I think they are measurements.
我还看到其他的东西
I see something else.
我看到
I see a...
一头美洲野牛
It's a bison.
美洲野牛对你们俩意味着什么吗
Does a bison mean anything to either of you?
那都是骗人的  在我这种人身上根本没用
It's hocus-pocus. It's never gonna work on a guy like me,
但如果你们想  我们可以试试
but we can try it if you want.
你们怎么坐到那边去了
How'd you guys get over there?
D·A·弗里蒙特货物
今早保安在这里找到他的
Security guard found him here this morning.
我们还没确认他的身份
We haven't ID'd him yet.
他的私人物品散落得到处都是
His personal effects are scattered everywhere,
所以我们找不到他的钱包
so we didn't find his wallet.
但是找齐他的公文包  也许就能找到钱包了
But we may find it when we find the rest of his briefcase...
还有他的断手
and his missing hand.
好吧
Well,
从撕开的肢体和爪痕来看
judging by that avulsion and the claw marks,
我认为是大型的掠食动物干的
I'd say a large predatory animal did this.
但不管是什么动物  它要有十厘米长的尖牙
But whatever it was would have to have four-inch canines,
咬合力为每127平方米  重达一吨
a bite force of 5,000 P.S.I., and weigh over a ton.
那种动物根本不存在
That animal doesn't exist.
到底是什么造成的
What the hell did this?
你不会认为...
You don't think...
你还记不记得以前
Do you remember back in the day
我们不会冷静地把一座石像
when we wouldn't calmly consider
看作是我们的头号疑犯
a stone statue our prime suspect?
我还真不记得
No, I actually don't.
血迹
Blood.
好了  朋友们
All right, my friend,
我们有肉  芝士  牛油果酱和啤酒
we got meats, we got cheeses, we got guac, we got beer.
当然还有我最爱的薯片
And of course... we got my favorite chips.
我们开始谈天说地吧  你的朋友来吗
Let's get this confab poppin'. Are your friends coming?
来  让我先校正一下多重宇宙全息投影仪
Yeah, let me just calibrate the multiverse holo-projector
然后就可以开始了
and we'll be on our way.
你的朋友是其他地球上的人吗
Your friends are from different Earths?
我就知道多重宇宙全息投影仪
You know, I would've thought "Multi-verse holo-projector"
会让你这么想  但是显然不是
would have given you that clue, but... apparently not.
没错  他们是其他地球上的人
Yes, they're from other Earths.
开始运行了
And we're off and... running.
让我来介绍一下
Well, allow me to make some ntroductions.
来自地球12  拥有四个博士学位
From Earth-12, the holder of four PhDs
《若一切毫无意义，我为何购买此书》的作者
and the author of the book "Everything is Meaningless,
这位就是
So Why Did I Buy This Book?", I give you...
哈里森·沃尔夫冈·威尔斯先生
Herr Harrison Wolfgang Wells.
-你好  威尔斯  -你好
- Guten Tag, Wells. - Guten Tag.
我真是想笑  你认为拯救
Do you know that it amuses me that you think that saving
你这渺小的世界如此重要
your tiny world matters
却不知整个多元宇宙最终难免会被
when the entire multiverse will inevitably be consumed
炽烈高温吞噬
in a fiery heat dess?
-丝哇  -是  我是说了丝哇
- "Dess"? - Ja, that's what I said, dess.
死亡
Death.
对  丝哇  你这人是笼丝吗
Yeah, dess. What are you, dess?
-好吧  -你一定是那个
- Yeah. - Oh, you must be
叫西斯科的小家伙
the little one that they call Cisco.
你也不算小啊
You're not that little.
我一米七  你好哇
I'm 5'7". Guten Tag.
好了  继续  来自地球47的
All right, moving on. Um, from Earth-47,
向你介绍下亿万富翁发明家
I give you the billionaire inventor
与出版业大亨
and publishing tycoon,
自由言论的急先锋
general champion of free speech,
H·洛萨里奥·威尔斯
H. Lothario Wells.
没错  继续来别停
That's right. Now keep that coming.
现在试试另外那个  不是开裆裤
Now try the other one on. No, not the crotchless,
那个  那个有豹纹的
that--the other-the leopard print.
怎么回事
What's going on?
他  有些其他私事
He's, uh, otherwise occupied.
哎呦
Oh, golly.
你在呢  真抱歉
There you are. My apologies.
看来你抓了我们一个现行
It appears that y'all have caught us red-handed
在这豪宅里半盛装舞会
here at the mansion on dress-up night.
你知道有话说得好
You know what they say:
高智商是最好的春药
intellect is the greatest aphrodisiac.
是哟  可没人说过这种话
Ja, so, nobody says that.
敬智商与性欲的崛起
Here's to rising IQs and libidos.
虽然不想拿两个人当模式  哈里
Hate to call two a pattern here, Harry,
但是你的朋友们是不是有些...
but aren't your friends just--
然后是来自地球22的末世废土
And from the post-apocalyptic landscape of Earth-22,
那里人类和机器融为一体以便生存
where man and machine have become one in order to survive,
这位是威尔斯2.0
I give you Wells 2.0.
好咯  咱们快点解决这事
Right-o. Let's make this quick.
收割者抢了我们的汽油补给
Reapers have raided our petrol supplies
偷走了我们的水箱
and stolen our water tanks.
我想要去把它们砸成碎片
I'd like to smash them to bits. -
-现在像是个派对了  -不要忘记我
- It's a party now. - Forget not about me!
我是  灰袍威尔斯
'Tis I, Wells the Grey!
抱歉  连接不好
Sorry. It's a bad connection.
是  那连接太讨人厌了
Ja, that was a terrible connection.
你干的漂亮
Good on ya.
那家伙太古怪了
That dude was strange.
-哈里  -什么
- Harry? - Yeah?
来一下
Sidebar.
我们要  去一下
We're gonna...sidebar.
所以  记得我说"交点朋友"吗
So, remember when I said "Make friends"?
我说的不是和你自己
I didn't mean with yourself.
是啊  他们超棒的  对不对
Yeah, they're great, aren't they?
还是多元宇宙中最聪明的头脑
And some of the brightest minds in all the multiverse--
而且也是些好伙计
and good company too, I might add.
我是说  那个哈里森·沃尔夫冈·威尔斯
I mean, that Harrison Wolfgang Wells?
超逗的
Guy's hilarious.
-咱们挺绝望的  -那是肯定了
- Look, we're desperate. - Sure we are.
所以我们应该给威尔斯委员会一个机会
So I think we should give the Council of Wells a chance.
-"威尔斯委员会"  -不错的名字吧
- "Council of Wells"? - Pretty good name, right?
-确实不错  -我知道  好了
- Yes, it is. - I know, all right.
-好了  -各位
- All right! - Fellas.
-各位  -你能不能...
- Fellas! - Will you...
-你来吧  -现在说明接下来
- No, do your thing. - Here's how it's gonna
-要做的事  -别  停
- go down- - Nein. Halt.
那个  你是不必要的
So, you are unnecessary...
所以  不想要你  所以  你去吧
well, so, not wanted, so... off you go.
你去吧  你去吧
Off you go. Off you go.
他还在这里  你去吧
He's still here. Off you go.
就算我也知道什么时候搭档太多了
Even I know when you got too many partners.
虽然我有一半是机械
And I may be half machine...
但你们都挺没用的
but you're all useless.
我想大家想说的是
I think what the fellas are trying to say here
他们喜欢独自工作
is that they prefer to work alone.
-不用你说  -我刚说了
- You don't say. - I just did.
-已经说了  -是  他刚说了
- Done just said. - Ja, he just said.
行  你享受你轧死的老鼠
Fine. You enjoy your roadkill.
我吃我喜欢的薯片
I'm gonna be eating my favorite chips.
我地球上也曾有过一个西斯科
We had a Cisco on my Earth once.
他可美味了
He was delicious.
他吃了另一个西斯科
He ate the other Cisco.
我还是...
I'm gonna... Hm?
让你和你玩吧
Leave you to you.
这块石头样本没有展现出任何独特的属性
So this stone sample shows absolutely no unique attributes
完全就是普通的花岗岩
of any kind-totally normal granite statue.
除了...
Except...
它在分子水平上充满了
it's filled with traces of the dark matter
暗物质痕迹
暗物质的痕迹  就好像被填满了一样
on a molecular level, as if it's been flooded with it.
那么  又是一个公车超能力者
So, another bus meta?
不知怎的  可以让
One that somehow brings
无生物变成活物
inanimate objects to life
然后用它们来杀人
and uses them to kill.
这么怎么可能有任何的  可能性
How can this possibly be... possible?
我的猜测是  这个超能力者可以
My best guess? This meta has the ability
在物体上印下精神印记
to leave a psychic imprint on objects--
类似某种通过潜意识的连接
a sort of telekinetic puppeteering
用念力操纵木偶
through a subconscious link.
真是太聪明了  34-25-34
That's really smart, 34-25-34.
-他刚说的是我的...  -没  别理他
- Did he just give my... - No, ignore him.
这个  你看
Um...well, look.
好消息是  咱们的枪有
The good thing is, our rifles have
"把雕像炸掉"的设定
a "Blow statues to hell" Setting,
所以当这个超能力者出现后
so when this meta does show up...
我们早就准备好了
we'll be ready.
我希望现在就能准备好
I hope we're ready now.
我们的受害者名叫吉姆·福克斯
Our victim's name is Jim Fox.
他是韦瑟比的拍卖商
He was an auctioneer at Wetherby's.
他被袭击的时候正在运送
He was transporting a Native American artifact
印第安人文物  就是不知道是哪个
when he was attacked. We just don't know which one.
等下  也许我们知道
Oh, wait. Maybe we do.
黑色北美野牛金属挂坠
一个北美野牛项链
A bison necklace.
拉尔夫  你在巴士上看到过北美野牛对吧
Ralph, you said you saw a bison on the bus, right?
我是说  这世界上可没有所谓的巧合
I mean...nothing in our world is a coincidence.
-平反了  -又没人说你撒谎了
- Vindicated. - No one said you were lying.
我可以从你的眼中看出来
I could see it in your eyes.
根据这个拍卖报告
According to this auction report,
项链被分成了三个部分
the necklace was separated into three pieces.
第一部分在公文包中  第三个位置
The first was in the briefcase, the third is unknown,
但是第二个在一个私人收藏家手上
but the second was in the hands of a private collector.
-"克里斯托夫银行"  -我去通知中城警局
- "Christoph Banks." - I'll get the CCPD.
找出他的地址  他也许有危险了
Get his address. He may be in danger.
那咱们最好去拜访一下他
Then we better pay him a visit.
-你准备好穿战服了吗  -当然
- You ready to suit up? - Oh, yeah.
我的战服在哪
Where's my suit?
这个仅仅是原型
Now, this is just a prototype,
自适应纳米组织结构
but she's got an adaptive nano-weave structure
非常具有  等下  延展性
that is--wait for it-malleable...
可以在分子水平延展
on a sub-molecular level.
不知道那是什么意思  也不在乎
Don't know what that means, don't care.
赶集拉掉这块布  我准备好穿超级战衣了
Just yank the tarp off. I'm ready for my super-suit.
拉尔夫
Ralph...
那块布就是你的超级战衣
this tarp is your super-suit.
你伸展时  它随之伸展
When you stretch, it stretches.
你收缩时  它随之收缩
When you squish, it squishes.
收缩成这么丑的样子
Squishes into something butt-ugly.
范儿和品味去哪儿了
Where's the style, the flair?
德比需要孔雀开屏
Dibny needs to peacock.
德比需要穿着西斯科
Dibny needs to wear the prototype
为他精心设计的战袍原型
Cisco so lovingly made for him.
要不  你就光着身子打击犯罪吧
Either that, or you fight crime naked.
不行  不能光着身子打击犯罪
Nope! Don't fight crime naked!
这是什么  小狗雨衣吗
What is this, a puppy's raincoat?
这些收藏让你眼界大开  是不是
The collection really is quite impressive, isn't it?
弄到这些要花的资金可不小
It's taken no small amount of resources to acquire.
我很高兴能与
I'm just glad to share it
懂得欣赏的人共同观赏
with someone who appreciates it.
-是啊  -那么  你写的这本书
- That I do. - So, this book you're writing.
是关于苏族手工艺品的吗
It's on Sioux artifacts?
我有苏族人血统  准确来说是拉科塔族
My entire bloodline is Sioux--Lakota, to be exact.
那你会喜欢这个的
Then you're gonna love this.
这个...
This...
是拉科塔和睦烟斗
is a Lakota peace pipe.
需要拆开修理
Had to have it taken apart and repaired
才能重新吸烟
so it can be smoked.
想试试吗
Wanna try it?
你称之为和睦烟斗的东西
That which you call a "Peace pipe"
完全不是一件东西
is no such thing.
那是提桑·维给予祈祷者的
It is a sacred gift for prayer
神圣礼物  她是提供了7项神圣权利的
from Ptesan-Wi, bringer of the seven sacred rights--
白色水牛少女
the White Buffalo Calf Woman.
你从不会把十字架倒过来祈祷
You'd never hang a Christian cross upside down...
也不会把美国国旗放在地板上
or lay an American flag on the floor.
但你却破坏了这神灵
Yet, you destroy that which is wakan--
用你肮脏的肉体触碰这神圣的物件
what is holy--by letting it touch your filthy flesh.
我会告诉你这无礼将带来何种后果
But I am here to teach you the price for your impudence.
你以为你是谁
Who do you think you are?
我是布莱克·柏森
I am the Black Bison.
够了
Enough.
这战衣才叫酷
Whoa. Now, that is a cool suit.
记得给西斯科拍几张照片
Remember to take some pics for Cisco.
救命  别丢下我
Help! Don't leave me!
你让她跑了
You let her get away.
从这里提取到的暗物质痕迹
I'm getting the same traces of dark matter from this
与老虎雕像里的一致
that I was from the tiger statue.
看来这个超能力者可不仅仅会
Looks like our meta isn't restricted
-激活雕像而已  -对
- to animating just stone. - No,
但她能力有局限
but she does have some limitations.
办公室里所有的工艺品
Out of all the artifacts in the office,
她只能控制那个骑士
she could only control the knight.
那也许她的通灵力
So then maybe her psychic imprint abilities
受限于肖像
are just restricted to effigies.
意思只是雕像而已
It just means "Statues."
我不知道
Yeah, I don't know.
我听着挺污的
Sounds kinda dirty to me.
所以如果雕像像人
So if the statues look like people
或动物  她就可以赋予他们生命力
or animals, she can bring them to life.
好消息是城里
Good thing there's only
只有上千座这样的雕像而已
thousands of those in the city.
面部识别这里有发现
Oh, I got a hit on facial recognition.
米娜·沙伊唐  文化人类学教授
"Mina Chaytan, professor of cultural anthropology"?
-她是老师吗  -曾经是
- She's a teacher? - Was.
她成了激进分子  但是在半年前
She became an activist, but she lost her job
中城警局逮捕记录
在被捕后丢了工作
six months ago after being arrested.
非法闯入  盗窃
Breaking and entering, trespassing, burglary--
挺激进的  指控撤销了
quite an activist. The charges were dropped,
但学校还是解雇她了
but the university still let her go.
她在试着拿回博物馆的几件苏族
She was trying to reclaim several Sioux art pieces
艺术展品  沙伊唐成为超能力者之前
from the museum. Chaytan was at this
就在这么做
even before she was a meta.
是啊  只是现在她把游戏升级为了命案
Yeah, except now she's upped her game to homicide.
她想要那项链的第三个部分吗
She wants the third piece of that necklace?
-那我们要先于她找到  -好
- Let's find it before she does. - Okay.
韦斯特父女要联手办案了
West and West are on the case.
你怎么了
What's wrong with you?
你让她跑了  本可以抓到她的
You let her get away. We could've caught her.
没错  但我救了班克斯的命
Yeah, I let her go, but I also saved Banks's life.
这是当时情况下最重要的事
That was the most important thing in that situation.
是吗  艾伦  因为对我而言
Really, Allen? Because to me,
我是警察时  抓住坏人
when I was a cop, getting the bad guy--
才是最重要的事
that was the most important thing.
你是闪电侠
You're the Flash.
你可以救他又抓住她
You could've saved him and caught her.
听着  拉尔夫
All right, look, Ralph.
我总是会做出
I'm always gonna make the decision
优先救人的决定
to help the person in danger first.
这是我们的职责
That's what we do here.
好吧  我们会把这个归档在
All right, well, we'll file that
"今日超级英雄教训"里的
under "Superhero lesson of the day," You know?
你看着像拔光了毛的鸡
You look like a plucked chicken.
伙计们
Guys, guys!
我还是觉得我们能做的最好的事
I still think the best thing we can do
是搞清楚迪沃的目的
is figure out what is Devoe's goal.
从那开始  我们可以追踪所有...
And then from there, we can track all--
那是单纯人的
That's a simple plan
单纯计划
from a simple man.
-你这话没什么用  -我们为什么不先用
- That's not helping. - Why don't we use
贝斯·诺威克的方法呢
the Bates-Novick method first?
我们确定出每个超能力者拥有各自超能力的原因
We determine why each meta developed their super powers...
然后把他们打成碎片
and then we smash them to bits.
我在这里见识过很多奇怪的事
I've seen a lot of strange here,
但这次可真是拔得头筹了啊
but...this takes all the cakes.
威尔士会议  怎么样了
Okay, Council of Wells! How we doing?
发现我们的神秘敌人了吗
Have we found our mystery foe yet?
没有  我们都还没能就使用方法达成一致
No, we can't even agree on what methodology to use.
-什么  -是的
- What? - Yes.
-都花了一天了  -我知道
- You've had an entire day. - I know.
-等等  -什么
- Wait. - What?
不是有三个你吗
Weren't there three of you?
谢谢那个旋转木马  亲爱的
Thanks for the merry-go-round, sweetheart.
你知道我的意思
You know what I mean.
抱歉  我之前得去搞定一些
Oh, sorry. I had to take care
私生活的事
of some off-camera business.
-天呐  -怎么了
- Oh, my God! - What? What?
我能看到你的小弟弟
I can see your frank and beans.
拜托
Come on, now.
我已经尽力往回收了  再说
I do my best thinking commando. Plus,
你们又不是没看过自己的那玩意
it ain't like we all haven't seen it before.
我没见过
I haven't seen it!
你们这些地球人太保守了
Ah, you Earth folk. You guys are so uptight.
-我可以  -我们能不能
- I--can... - Can we just
回到手头的任务上来  我们需要答案
get back to the task at hand? We need answers.
最好的答案就是最简单的
The best answer is always the simplest.
为什么不去找出每一个迪沃
Why don't we go to every Devoe we can find...
然后审问他们
and interrogate 'em?
婴儿时期的迪沃也要吗
What, even the baby Devoe?
特别是婴儿时期的他
Especially the baby Devoe.
婴儿暴力解决不了任何问题
Baby violence solves nothing.
大伙们
Guys--guys...
好了  先生们
All right--gentlemen!
很明显这路行不通  顺便一说
Clearly, this isn't working. And by the way,
问题不是我  是你们
it's not me. It's you.
这...
This...
可真是个馊主意
was a bad idea.
感觉你的那玩意儿已经深深印在我脑子里了
It's like your junk has been burned into my brain.
不客气
You're welcome.
我们找到了项链的第三个碎片
We've got the third piece of the necklace.
我爸爸发现碎片在中城博物馆展览
My dad found out that it was on display at Central City Museum,
但当他们想明白
but when they figured out
碎片是目标时...
that it was a target...
中城博物馆
碎片已经被运走了
It's on the move.
是的  碎片被放在武装车辆上
Yeah, it's being transferred via armored car
运往布鲁克菲尔德山庄一处安全存放设施
to a secure storage facility in Brookfield Heights.
-我锁定了卡车的坐标  -好的
- I pinged the truck's GPS. - All right.
拉尔夫  咱们走
Ralph? Let's go.
我去换那件丑战衣
I'll get my ugly suit.
小猫咪
Kittens.
你好
Hello.
你准备好坐牢了吗
Are you ready to go to jail?
这东西不属于拍卖行
This doesn't belong in an auction house.
它不该埋没在某个人的收藏里
It doesn't belong in someone's collection.
它属于苏族人  我的族人
It belongs to the Sioux people... my people.
米娜  我知道你经历了很多事
Mina...I know you've been through a lot,
但这不是解决问题的方...
but this is not the way to--
我再也不用听你这种人的了  闪电侠
I don't need to listen to men like you anymore, Flash.
几周之前  我体内发生了变化
A few weeks ago, something inside me changed...
我变得更厉害  更强大了
changed for the better... for the more powerful.
现在只有黑色野牛了
And now there's just the Black Bison.
你休想跑
Oh, no, you don't.
电线  带那些人去安全的地方
The power lines! Get those people clear.
但我能抓住她
But I can catch the meta!
劳拉
Laura!
说了我能抓住她
Told you I'd get her.
电停了
Hey, the power's out.
救命
Help!
-劳拉  -我快举不住了
- Laura! - I can't keep holding it up.
劳拉
Laura!
急救就快到了
EMTs are almost here.
我抱住她了
I got her.
她还有呼吸
She's still breathing.
好了  快醒过来  宝贝
Come on, wake up, honey.
宝贝  快醒过来
Honey, come on! Wake up!
天啊  天啊  醒过来  宝贝
Oh, God, oh, God. Wake up, honey.
天啊  宝贝  亲爱的  醒过来
Oh, God, honey. Honey, wake up.
醒过来  宝贝
Come on, honey.
你先好好休息  好吗
Okay, you just rest up, okay?
我一会儿再回来看你  马上就来
I'm gonna come back and check on you in a little while.
轻微脑震荡
Well, mild concussion,
腿部有丝状骨折
a hairline fracture in her leg.
她很年轻  很快就会好的
She's young. She'll heal fast.
-好吧  -谢谢你  医生
- Okay. - Thank you, doctor.
不客气  但是考虑到这次意外
You're very welcome. But, considering the accident,
她能活下来真是万幸
she's very lucky to be alive.
拉尔夫  我们得谈谈
Look, Ralph. We need to talk.
-你不能...  -别说
- You can't-- - Don't.
别再提了  好吗
Just...just forget it, okay?
伙计
Hey, buddy.
你是想重新叫那群家伙回来吗
You planning on bringing the band back together,
我要不要把极速实验室清理出来
or should I clear out the Speed Lab?
去他的  我们不需要那个无能者委员会
Broom it. We don't need that Council of Incompetents.
我们现在这么称呼他们了吗
Is that what we're calling them now?
因为我清楚地记得你说
'Cause, uh, I distinctly remember you saying
他们是"所有宇宙中最聪明的人"
they were "the brightest minds in all the multiverse."
也是最烦人的
And the most annoying.
我以为如果身边都是和我一样的人
I thought if I surrounded myself with people like me,
我会喜欢他们  但我不喜欢他们
I would like them. I don't like them.
我讨厌他们  讨厌他们所有人
I hate them. I hate them all.
这话太狠了
Strong words.
你也见过他们了  拉蒙
You saw them, Ramon, right?
那个沃尔夫冈·威尔斯  他总是在纠正别人
That Wolfgang Wells? He's always correcting people--
超级烦人的毛病  另一个人
an extremely annoying habit. The other guy--
"漏阴狂"威尔斯  他太自以为是了
the "Free Willy" Wells? He's so full of himself.
还有另一个  半机械人威尔斯
And the other, Cyborg Wells?
你知道他怎么失去眼睛的吗
You know how he lost his eye?
他女儿在冬至对抗赛上挖出来的
His daughter gouged it out at the Solstice Combat Games.
我不怪罪她
I don't blame her.
要是我也会这么做
I'd have done the same.
我很想把他另一只眼也挖出来
I'd like to gouge out the other eye.
-哈里  -干什么
- Harry. - What?
你知道  你基本上是在
You know you're essentially
抱怨你自己  对吗
complaining about yourself, right?
拉蒙
Ramon...
请你尽量仔细听我说的话
do your best to pay attention to the conversation.
我才没有在抱怨我自己
I'm not complaining about myself.
我是在抱怨他们
I'm complaining about them.
没错  他们是我的二重身  我们长得挺像
Yes, we're doppelgangers. We look alike.
但我们的性格截然不同
We have completely different personalities.
那么你不觉得
So, you don't think
你会马上纠正别人
you can be quick to correct people?
你不觉得你不会自以为是吗
You don't think you can be full of yourself?
自以为是  才不会  我多牛啊
Full of myself? No, I'm amazing.
我简直完美  我说的是他们
I'm fantastic. I'm talking about them.
我不喜欢他们  我讨厌他们
I don't like them. I hate them.
讨厌他们所有人
I hate them all.
你知道我怎么想吗
You know what I think?
我觉得这完全都是因为你自己
I think this is entirely about yourself.
我认为隐藏在你的抱怨和潜意识之下的
I think underneath all your brain and bluster,
其实是你对自己的不满
you actually don't have a very high opinion of yourself.
什么
What?
你为什么觉得交新朋友这么难呢
Why do you think it's so hard for you to make new friends?
我可不觉得我交友困难
I don't have a hard time...
哈里
Harry.
如果你不喜欢自己  没人会喜欢你的
No one's gonna like you if you don't like yourself first.
那里的那些怪胎  他们
These weirdos over here, they...
他们没必要回应我们的求救信号
they didn't have to answer our call for help.
但他们回应了  因为你也会这样做
But they did...'cause you would've done the same.
没错  你确实有非常讨人厌非常粗鲁的一面
And yes, there are some really annoying, rough parts of you,
但你知道吗
but you know what?
我也见过你非常了不起的面孔
I've seen some amazing parts too.
因为有时候你是个强人  是个英雄
'Cause sometimes, you're a hard-ass, you're a hero.
有时候  你又是个巫师  哈里
Sometimes... you're a wizard, Harry.
威尔斯委员会
The Council of Wells...
如果你想要它起作用
if you wanna make that work...
你就得用更高的热情对待自己
you have to start treating yourself with some compassion.
对待所有的你
All of yourselves.
现在又到了让简单哈里
Now is the time that Simple Harry has come
继续羞辱我们的时候了
to insult us even more?
我不是要羞辱你的  我是来...
I didn't call to insult. I called to...
-道歉的  -道歉
- Apologize. - Apologize?
在碎脸人科隆的统治下
Apologizing is punishable by banishment
道歉是要被放逐的
under Krung the Face-Crusher!
好吧  这太不幸了
All right, well... that's unfortunate.
听着  我知道你们几个更愿意独自工作
Look, I know you guys prefer to work alone.
你们不想与其他人一起工作
You don't wanna work with other people.
觉得自己太聪明  能甩别人好几条街
You think you're so smart, you can just push them away,
我知道这想法  因为我也是你们
and I can say that because I'm one of you,
但如果我们想要找到我们的迪沃
but if we're going to find our DeVoe...
那我们就必须合作
then we have to work together.
我们必须像
We have to work as...
-朋友  -朋友
- Friends. - Friends...
-炮友  -是  不  不是那样
- with benefits? - Yeah, no, we're not doing that,
但我相信  我们都能从彼此身上
but I'm sure we can all find something
发掘到自己欣赏的东西
that we like in one another--
比如说你  威尔斯2.0版  很明显你
like you, Wells 2.0. You're clearly very...
资源好能力强  还有你
resourceful and strong. And you,
你特别有感召力
you're extremely charismatic.
我相信你能为自己的研究团队
I'm sure you can recruit top talent
招揽到天才
to your research teams.
原来我是负责招揽天才的
Oh, I bring the talent.
没错  还有你
Yeah--and you,
威尔斯先生  你非常的
Herr Wells, you're very...
-低调  -是的  很显然
- blunt. - Ja. Obviously.
-是  那我们能不能  你们能不能
- Right, but can we just-- can you...
当然  没问题  抱歉老兄
Yeah, sure. And I'm sorry, man.
我之前说的关于你的  你懂的
What I said before about your...you know,
就是你的那套微型连环杀手
your theory on the behavioral upbringings
事儿逼难相处的行为教育理论
of nano-serial killers being un-chill--
这么说有点过了  我不该这么说
that was uncalled for. I shouldn't have said that.
真是相当妙的理论  恭喜你
It's a very groovy theory. Good on you.
是的  谢谢
Ja--uh, danke.
我认为我之前说的
I suppose that when I said that
你在《分子精神病学》上
your theory on narcotics
有关毒品的理论
in molecular psychiatry was stupider
比小婴儿的理论还要蠢之类的话
than a theory made by tiny babies,
同样说的太过头了
that that was uncalled for also.
-这就对了  -是  我现在就在营造
- There we go. - Yeah, and I'm digging
这种半人半金属的诡异氛围
the whole creepy half-man, half-metal vibe
-到你了  -我只想说
- you got going on. - I just wanna say...
对你们所有人
all of you...
我真的对你们每个人
I really respect the fact
都有两只眼睛这件事
that each one of you...
充满了敬意
has two eyes.
没错  好吧
Yeah--hey, well, um,
我们都达成了某种一致  很好
we all agree on something. That's great.
所以就这点而言  我在此重新召集
So, on that note, I hereby reconvene
威尔斯委员会的各位  现在关于迪沃
the Council of Wells. Now, about our DeVoe...
就迪沃的事  如果我们当初能用我的
Well, about DeVoe-- perhaps if we were to combine
统计学消除模型让贝斯·诺威克
the Bates-Novick of our mutant friend here
和我们这位变异朋友联合
with my models of statistical elimination...
我能帮上你的忙  也许我们可以用
I'll do you one more. Maybe we enhance
根据迪沃先前行动建立起来的心理学档案
your elimination models with a psych profile
来强化你的消除模型
based on DeVoe's previous action.
我就能得出一套预测算法
I could whip up a predictive algorithm.
-对  对  -然后在我的
- Ja, ja, ja, ja. - Run it through
量子大脑芯片里运行这套算法
my quantum cerebral chip,
我们就能马上找到他
we'll find him in no time.
我现在明白了  你为什么会叫上这些人
- I'm starting to see why you called these guys.
没错
Yeah.
好了  先生们
All right, gentlemen.
我们开工吧
Let's get to work.
拉尔夫·德比
私家侦探所
如果你是来跟我说  我搞砸了
If you're here to tell me how I royally screwed up,
害那个小女孩受伤了
letting that little girl get hurt...
相信我  我都知道
trust me...I know.
我一直以来都在感受着
I keep feeling all these feelings--
愧疚  悔恨  心痛
guilt...remorse...heartburn.
好吧  最后的那一样我帮不上你
Well, I can't help you with that last one,
但其他两样我没准能帮上忙
but maybe I can help with the rest.
-这些是什么  -以前的案子
- What are all those? - Past cases.
这些案子都很简单
Those were simpler times.
丈夫背着妻子出轨  妻子背着丈夫出轨
Husband stepping out on wife, wife stepping out on husband...
丈夫同时背着妻子和丈夫出轨
husband stepping out on wife and husband.
这一件案子稍微复杂点
That one was a little less simple.
拉尔夫  你想要说什么
Ralph, it was like you were gonna make a point?
我想说的重点是
My point is...
我以前当私家侦探的时候  我
when I was a P.I., I...
我不用去担心什么医院里的小女孩
I didn't have to worry about little girls in hospitals.
我只用去搜集污点
I just had to get the dirt.
之后发生的事  我就不用知道了
Whatever happened after that, I wasn't there to see it.
而现在  我满眼都能见到受伤的人
Now all I see are people getting hurt
或者将要受伤的人
or about to get hurt.
那五年当中
And then for five years,
我不用去关心任何人
I got by without caring about anyone.
而现在我却要去关心整座城市的人吗
Now I have to care about a whole city?
这是这份工作的一部分  拉尔夫
It's a part of the job, Ralph.
或许要算最重要的一部分
Maybe the most important part.
你怎么做到的
How do you do it?
你怎么在明知这些人
How do you walk around knowing
未来遭遇的情况下  还能这么泰然处之
what could happen to all those people?
我并不是每次都能处理好
I...don't always handle it well.
我也做过很糟糕的决定
I've made bad decisions,
有时候还会让更多的人受伤
and sometimes it got more people hurt.
你只需要尽自己全力
You just gotta do the best you can.
如果这样还不够
And when that's not enough,
你就去依靠你身边的人
you lean on the people around you.
你  是在说依靠你吗
Oh...you... you mean you.
对  我  拉尔夫
Yeah, me, Ralph.
听着  我把你带进来是因为我认为
Look, I brought you into this because I think that
你有成为英雄的品质  但我不会打包票
you have the makings of a hero, but I would be lying
跟你说一切都会变得顺顺当当
if I said there won't be hard days.
日子难过的时候
And when there are,
你就需要有谁帮你一把
you need someone to turn to.
我可以扮演这个角色
I can be that person...
如果你愿意的话
if you want.
你会为我这么做
You'd do that for me?
我会把扞卫你的心灵这件事
I will make it my personal mission
当作我的私人任务
to protect your heart.
听着  拉尔夫  其实我觉得
Look, Ralph, I-I actually think it's great
你现在经历下这些感受也挺好的
you're feeling all this stuff.
但别忘了
But don't forget:
那个小女孩会没事的
that little girl is gonna be okay.
我们也抓到了坏人
And we got the bad guy.
没错
Yeah.
我们抓到了坏人
We got the bad guy.
中城警局
我不知道你从哪儿来的吗
Don't I know you from somewhere?
-你不知道  -不  我知道
- Not likely. - No, I do.
我是在去年的那些抗议活动之后逮捕的你
I arrested you after one of those protests last year.
别碰我
Don't touch me.
那些工艺品的去处是博物馆
Those artifacts are headed for the museum.
而等监狱长来的时候
And once the warden's people get here,
你的去处就是铁山监狱了
you're headed to Iron Heights.
先生们  情尽情享受这场视觉盛宴
Gentlemen, feast your eyes on this wonder.
这个坏小子全身上下
This bad boy is replete
都涂满了聚合物  还穿着防火盔甲
with polymer-coated, flame-resistant armor,
正面碰撞偏转板
frontal impact deflection panels,
和双重过滤防毒面具
a dual-filtered gas mask--
这样他就不会吸入自己制造的有毒物质
so you don't cry on your own supply.
尤其是这个小玩意儿
Especially with this bad boy.
洋葱枪
Call it the Onion.
大家有问题吗
Any questions?
是时候去拿回属于我们的东西了
It's time we go collect what's ours.
乔刚来电话说
Joe just called.
谢坦从中城警局逃走了
Chaytan escaped from CCPD.
很显然  她还在警局安插了一款
Apparently, she made a tactical dummy
终结者一样的假人模型
go full "Terminator" at the station.
我们知道她要去哪
Well, we know where she's going.
-那串项链  -她之前偷的两部分
- The necklace. - The two pieces she stole
已经跟第三部分合上了  放在博物馆里
have been reunited with the third piece at the museum.
她之前就为项链杀过人
She has killed for these before.
这次她也会杀了所有妨碍她拿回项链的人
She will kill anyone that gets in her way to reclaim them.
现在要靠我们了  你准备好了吗
It's up to us. Are you ready?
我在你说那个之前都是准备好的
Well... I was until you said that.
-你什么  -不是吧  老兄
- What are you... - Jeez Louise, man.
想想你说的那堆像《勇敢的心》的话好吧
What kind of rousing "Braveheart" Speech was that?
-赶紧去把你衣服穿上  -能帮帮我吗
- Just put your thing on. - Wanna help me?
-不  -真的很紧
- No. - It's really tight.
快点
Hurry up!
你好  美人
Hello, beautiful.
把项链摘下来  米娜
Put it down, Mina.
那是属于博物馆的财产
That belongs in a museum.
这就是博物馆
This is a museum.
我说完了才意识到是
I realized that after I said it.
确实  你们把它作为美国历史的
Yes. You keep it here as
一部分保存在这里
part of American history.
但我们不是历史  我们还活在世上
But we're not history. We are still here...
依然神圣  如同这条项链一样
still sacred, as is this necklace.
它得回归苏族人的手中
It's going back to the Sioux.
闪开
Get out of my way.
在你伤害了那么多人之后不可能了  米娜
Not after the people you've hurt, Mina.
也不会再让你伤害别人了
And you're not gonna hurt anyone else.
真的吗
Is that so?
别动
Don't move.
它们的视觉是基于物体运动的
Their vision is based on movement.
那部电影简直充满谎言
That movie is filled with lies!
现在有条霸王龙在追我们
We have a T. Rex.
里面出什么事了
What's going on in here?
别动  我逮到你了
Stop! I got you.
你准备怎么办  超级英雄
Whatcha gonna do, super hero?
看在杰夫·高布伦的份上  停手
For the love of Jeff Goldblum, stop!
你真是永远不打算停止追我了  对不对
You're really never going to stop chasing me, are you?
不  我并没有
No, I'm really not.
你知道在这里我可以让多少东西
Do you have any idea how many things
起死回生吗
I can bring to life in this place?
房顶上的石像怪
The gargoyles on the roof.
墙上的浮雕
The reliefs carved into the walls
以及承重柱
and support pillars.
苏族献祭碗
我可以在几秒钟内让这里
I can bring this whole place down
-整个塌陷掉  -但你不会这样做
- in a matter of seconds. - But you won't,
因为这里有一件你比复仇
because there is one thing you care about
更在乎的东西  对吗
more than vengeance, isn't there?
我都有点不相信你居然真的上套了
I kind of can't believe you fell for that.
来吧
Come on.
你差点就让她逃走了
You almost let her escape.
这个
Well...
我的耳边一直回荡着你叫我
I kept hearing your stupid voice
保护无辜者的愚蠢声音
telling me to protect the innocent.
干得漂亮  菜鸟
Nice job...rookie.
乖  在这好好待着
Good boy. Stay.
好的  听着不错  我会告知大家的
All right, sounds good. I'll let everybody know.
刚刚是乔打来的电话
Hey. That was Joe.
他说沃夫监狱长把沙伊唐关到
He says that Warden Wolfe has Chaytan locked up
铁山监狱去了  远离任何人体模特
at Iron Heights--far, far away from any mannequins,
-雕像  或者  -塑像
- statues, or-- - Effigies.
特意查了一下
Looked it up.
还是觉得说出来有点污
Still say it sounds kind of dirty,
但我毕竟不是字典通  所以无所谓了
but I'm not the mayor of the dictionary, so whatever.
乔还说现场清理人员
Joe also said that the cleanup crew
在博物馆里依然没找到那条野牛项链
at the museum still hasn't found the bison necklace.
我猜某人或许把项链寄回
Guess somebody might have mailed it back
苏族人保留地了
to the Sioux reservation.
某人
Somebody?
你又准备对我大吼大叫了吗
You gonna yell at me again?
不  这次不准备
No, not for this one.
米娜的朋友和家人
Mina's friends and family...
他们承受了太久的苦难
they've been hurt for too long.
我不确定你之前是否听过同样的话
And I'm not sure if you've heard this saying before,
但  超级英雄的首要职责就是保护众人
but...a superhero's first job is to protect people.
睿智之言
Wise words.
想喝咖啡吗  我请客
You want a coffee--on me?
这次我真请客
For real this time.
谢了  但
Thanks, but...
我得去照顾一个小女孩
I gotta see about a girl.
小家伙
Hey, kid.
你感觉怎么样
How you doing?
好多了  谢谢
Better, thanks.
那
That...
那太棒了
that's awesome.
但我真的好无聊
But I'm really bored.
是啊
Yeah...
你喜欢气球动物吗
Do you like balloon animals?
下面做个长颈鹿吧
Do a giraffe next.
好的  但  那个或许得用下脚趾
Okay, but...that might take some toes.
-怎么了  -我们觉得我们知道他的身份了
- What's going on? - We think we know who he is.
根据哈里的朋友所述
According to Harry's friends,
我们要找的人叫克利福德
the name we're looking for is Clifford...
克利福德·迪沃
Clifford DeVoe.
与我们的心理侧写百分之九十二吻合
92% match to our psychological profile.
没有其他叫迪沃的更接近了
No other DeVoe comes close.
这家伙很低调
Guy keeps a low profile.
没有社交网络痕迹  没有犯罪记录
No social media, no criminal record...
而且我们知道他藏身何处
And we know where he's hiding.
希巴尔德街43号
43 Hibbard Lane.
如果他如你所说那么危险
Well, if he's as dangerous as you said...
我可以打电话给辛格队长  派一队人过去
I can call Singh. We can get a squad over there.
不用
No.
我们去抓他吧
Let's go get him.
伙计们  斯旺  极速  萨维塔
Guys, Thawne, Zoom, Savitar...
头一次  我们真正有机会
for once, we actually have a chance here
能先敌人一步了
to get ahead of our enemy.
让我们去抓迪沃吧
Let's go get DeVoe.
有客人来了
We're about to have guests.
那就准备好跟他们打个招呼
Then let's be ready to greet them.
是这里吗
Is this the place?
就是这里了
This is the one.
-都准备好了吗  -"天眼"准备好了
- Is everyone set? - "Eye in the Sky" is a go.
前门也盯着在了
I have eyes on the front door.
斯诺和冰霜杀手待命中
Snow and Frost standing by.
你下令我们就冲进去
Just give us the word and we'll breach in.
怎样的犯罪首脑会在门口
What kind of criminal mastermind
放欢迎脚垫
has a welcome mat?
你好  有什么可以效劳的吗
Hi. Can I help you?
是的  女士
Yes, ma'am.
我是中城警局的乔·韦斯特警探
I'm Detective Joe West, CCPD.
这位是我同事巴里·艾伦
This is Barry Allen, my associate.
有什么问题吗
Is everything all right?
是的  我们想跟
Yes, we were just hoping
克利福德·迪沃聊聊  他在家吗
to talk with Clifford DeVoe. Is he here?
是的  他在家
Yes, he is.
我能问下是关于什么事吗  警官
May I ask what this is about, officers?
我们只是想问他几个问题
We just need to ask him some questions.
出什么事了吗  我丈夫惹什么麻烦了吗
Is something wrong? Is my husband in trouble?
-你丈夫  -没有  女士
- Your husband? - No, ma'am.
克利福德
Clifford.
警察来了  他们想找你聊聊
The police are here. They'd like a word.
谢谢  亲爱的
Thank you, dear.
下午好  先生们
Good afternoon, gentlemen.
我叫克利福德·迪沃
I'm Clifford DeVoe.
有什么能效劳的吗
How may I be of help?